europeupclose.com 2018-03-03

# Privacy Policy - Europe Up Close

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you send a contact form, comment on a blog or subscribe to a newsletter. You may, however, visit this site anonymously.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information that is collected from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience:  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve this website:  
We continually strive to improve this website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service:  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To process transactions:  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails:  
The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your commission/order.

 **Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please respond to said email and indicate your request to “unsubscribe.”

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server (PayPal.com) when purchasing. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Will any information be disclosed to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating this website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other’s rights, property, or safety.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on this website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of this site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. This website, products and services are all directed to people who are 13 years of age or older

## Online privacy policy only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through this website and not to information collected offline.

## Your consent

By using this site, you consent to this Privacy Policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contacting me

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact the website administrator [here](http://europeupclose.com/contact/).
